<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Guidelines on Cupper</title>
    <link>https://thepaciellogroup.github.io/cupper/tags/guidelines/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Guidelines on Cupper</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
	<atom:link href="https://thepaciellogroup.github.io/cupper/tags/guidelines/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>ADA</title>
      <link>https://thepaciellogroup.github.io/cupper/patterns/guidelines/ada/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thepaciellogroup.github.io/cupper/patterns/guidelines/ada/</guid>
      <description> Americans with Disabilities Act https://www.essentialaccessibility.com/blog/ada-guidelines/
ADA DOJ
 Currently there are no specific guidelines https://adata.org/learn-about-ada  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Section 508</title>
      <link>https://thepaciellogroup.github.io/cupper/patterns/guidelines/section-508/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thepaciellogroup.github.io/cupper/patterns/guidelines/section-508/</guid>
      <description>Section 508 Federal Government standards
Not updated for ~20 years
Section 508 Refresh - Section 508 update - WCAG Level A and Level AA - January 18, 2018</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>WCAG 2.0</title>
      <link>https://thepaciellogroup.github.io/cupper/patterns/guidelines/wcag-2.0/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thepaciellogroup.github.io/cupper/patterns/guidelines/wcag-2.0/</guid>
      <description>Web Content Accessibility Guidelines 2.0 In the Summer of 2018, WCAG 2.0 will be extended to WCAG 2.1. Until then, the current guidelines are WCAG 2.0
Layers of Guidance Several layers of guidance are provided by WCAG in order to help individuals and organizations meet varying needs. These layers are:
 Principles: 4 principles that provide the foundation for web accessibility: perceivable, operable, understandable, and robust Guidelines: Within the 4 principles, there are 12 non-testable guidelines the provide basic goals authors should follow Success Criteria: Each guideline contains testable success criteria, with 3 levels of conformance: A, AA, AAA Sufficient and Advisory Techniques: For each of the guidelines and success criteria, techniques are documented and fall into two categories: those that are sufficient for meeting the success criteria and those that are advisory.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>WCAG 2.1</title>
      <link>https://thepaciellogroup.github.io/cupper/patterns/guidelines/wcag-2.1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://thepaciellogroup.github.io/cupper/patterns/guidelines/wcag-2.1/</guid>
      <description>Web Content Accessibility Guidelines 2.1 https://www.w3.org/TR/WCAG21/
WCAG 2.1 extends WCAG 2.0 by adding new success criteria, definitions to support them, guidelines to organize the additions, and a couple of additions to the conformance section.
The following Success Criteria are new in WCAG 2.1:
 1.3.4 Identify Common Purpose 1.3.5 Identify Purpose 1.4.10 Reflow 1.4.11 Non-Text Contrast 1.4.12 Text Spacing 1.4.13 Content on Hover or Focus 2.2.6 Timeouts 2.2.7 Animation from Interactions 2.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>